<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Qofi</string>
    <!--Main Buttons-->
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="gotit">Got it, let\'s go!</string>
    <string name="countme">Count me in!</string>
    <string name="change">CHANGE</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="giveme">Give me more</string>


    <!--Introduction Strings-->
    <string name="intro1head">Welcome to Qofi</string>
    <string name="intro1desc">Explore through the whole application by select each section of coffee knowledge</string>
    <string name="intro2head">New Era of Coffee Tour</string>
    <string name="intro2desc">Qofi offers you an enjoyable experience of coffee touring with great accessibility</string>
    <string name="intro3head">Sipping through Nature &amp; City</string>
    <string name="intro3desc">Qofi provided a glossary of what you can expect from the coffee scene in the world</string>
    <string name="intro4head">Qualified as a New User</string>
    <string name="intro4desc">Now you\'re in lad! Let\'s seek into the coffee universe and enjoy Qofi with a cup of coffee</string>
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_browse">Browse</string>
    <string name="nav_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="nav_profile">Profile</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="liberica_desc">Liberica is another species of coffee bean from Cofffea liberica trees in western, and central Africa. Liberica coffee beans originated from Liberia and naturalized in Asia continent such as Philippines, and Indonesia. Until now, Liberica is a small crop in the Phillippines and their beans tend to have smoky, nutty, dark chocolate notes when roasted and brewed. Liberica has run into near extinction in the 19th century where coffee industries in the city of Lipa collapsed. Liberica is also named as Manly Coffee in the Philippines.\n\nNowadays people struggle to find pure Liberica and support the efforts to keep it as a distinct species and irreplaceable part of the coffee genome. Liberica beans can be huge and have the unique characteristic in which many Liberica beans are asymmetric - one side is \"lower\" than the other, causing a little \"hook\" at the bottom of the bean. It is the only bean species in the world with this irregular shape.
Its almond-shaped beans have an exceptional aroma, almost floral and fruity, while its flavor is full and slightly smokey. This is a highly polarizing coffee bean.
</string>
    <string name="robusta_desc">Robusta is the next species of coffee bean with low acidity, high bitterness, and high amount of antioxidants. Robusta coffee beans came from the Coffea canephora plant in central and western sub-Saharan Africa. It represents 40% of global coffee production. While roasted robusta beans provide a strong coffee flavor, which has double the caffeine of Arabica.
Robusta coffee beans are easier to care for and has a greater crop yield that cause them cheaper to produce and as a bug resistant because caffeine in Robusta has a role as a natural defense against pests. Because of its vigor and ease of care, Robusta in, unfortunately, the coffee of choice in areas not well-suited to growing coffee. It can be forced to grow in extremely sub-optimal environments, even by farmers who have no idea what they\'re doing. For the best Robusta, choose one whose description emphasizes that it was grown in a suitable area by farmers who know what they\'re doing. When serving Robusta, feel free to take advantage of its versatility. Because a good Robusta can stand up to any amount of milk and sugar, and makes a darn fine cup of iced coffee. It\'s also the secret ingredient in many a fancy espresso since Robusta enhances crema significantly.</string>
    <string name="pourover_desc">Hot water is hand poured over a bed of coffee grounds and drips through a paper filter using gravity. This single-cup manual method is popular with baristas who are keen on controlling every aspect of the brew.</string>
    <string name="espressomachine_desc">A typical espresso machine uses nine bars of pressure to force water through a bed of finely ground coffee and a filter. The resulting shot of coffee is syrupy and highly concentrated.</string>
    <string name="mokapot_desc">Invented in Italy, the moka pot is an aluminium stove-top brewer popular in Europe that uses pressure to force hot water through finely ground coffee. The unfiltered brew is highly concentrated like espresso and often has crema.</string>
    <string name="thepress_desc">This immersion method involves letting coffee grounds soak in hot water before straining or pressing the brew through a metal filter. Pressed coffee is usually thick in texture due to the sediment that remains in the brew.</string>
    <string name="siphon_desc">Invented in Europe in the mid-19<sup>th</sup> century, the siphon, or vacuum coffee maker, is an elaborate immersion brewing device made of glass that uses vapour pressure to force hot water into ground coffee.</string>
    <string name="cezve_desc">Also known as an ibrik, a cezve is a Turkish coffee pot. This small vessel is typically made of copper and is used to heat finely ground coffee and water over a flame or on a hob resulting in a thick, rich, concentrated brew.</string>
    <string name="jebena_desc">A traditional clay Jebena is used in an Ethiopian coffee ceremony. The coffee is roasted immediately before brewing, hand-ground using a pestle and mortar, and then brewed directly in a jebena over hot coals.</string>
    <string name="espressotype_desc">Espresso is a small, concentrated, syrupy shot of coffee that is achieved when pressure is used to force water through finely ground coffee from Italy. Espresso is generally thicker than coffee brewed by other methods and has a higher concentration of suspended and dissolved solids. Espresso has more caffeine than most coffee beverages despite the usual serving size is much smaller. Espresso is made by forcing very hot water under high pressure through finely ground compacted coffee. Tamping down the coffee promotes the water\'s even penetration through the grounds.</string>
    <string name="americanotype_desc">Americano is an espresso with hot water or filtered coffee that giving similar strength to, but different flavor from other traditional brewed coffees from Italy. The term is American coffee with a 1:1 espresso/water ratio. Americano have varies of caffeine strength depends with the number of shots of espresso and the amount of water added. Americano usually is used when one orders a brew-coffee sized drink from an espresso bar.</string>
    <string name="macchiatotype_desc">Macchiato is an espresso coffee drink with a small amount of steamed milk. It’s called stained coffee in Italy. The name was come from baristas needing to show the serving waiters the difference between an espresso and an espresso with a tiny bit of milk in it. Macchiato is typically prepared by pouring a small amount of foamed milk directly into a single shot or espresso and has the highest ratio of espresso to milk of any drink made with those ingredients.</string>
    <string name="cappuccinotype_desc">Cappuccino is an espresso-based coffee from Italy prepared with double espresso and steamed milk foam. Cappuccino does involve the use of cream instead of milk,and add extra flavor with cinnamon or chocolate powder. Cappuccino has smaller volume of micro foam layer on the top. Today, cappuccinos are most often prepared with an espresso machine. The double espresso is poured into the bottom of the cup, followed by a similar amount of hot milk, which is prepared by heating and texturing the milk using the espresso machine steam wand. The top third of the drink consists of milk foam.</string>
    <string name="flatwhitetype_desc">Flat white is a coffee drink consisting of espresso with micro foam. It\’s like caffè latte, but smaller in volume and with less micro foam, therefore having a higher proportion of coffee to milk, and milk that is velvety in consistency – allowing the espresso to dominate the flavor, while being supported by the milk. This term was come from a documented reference to the beverage dates to Australia in the mid-1980s at Moors Espresso Bar in Sydney. It\’s essentially the opposite of a \"dry cappuccino\", which has dry frothy foam but no liquid milk. A flat white has milk (or micro foam) but no froth. The milk should be velvety rather than fluffy and therefore stronger, which requires a shorter, ristretto espresso shot to avoid harsh flavors. The flat white is like an original Italian cappuccino, which is a single espresso with micro foam.</string>
    <string name="mochatype_desc">Mocha is an espresso blended with chocolate syrup and topped with steamed milk or micro foam. Another term is called mocaccino, from the city of Mocha, Yemen which was one of the centers of early coffee trade. Mocha can also be referred to as hot chocolate with espresso added. Like cappuccino, mochas typically contain the distinctive milk froth on top, although, as is common with hot chocolate, they are sometimes served with whipped cream instead. They are usually topped with a dusting of either cinnamon or cocoa powder, and marshmallows may also be added on top for flavor and decoration.</string>
    <string name="lattemacchiatotype_desc">Latte macchiato is a coffee where the milk is stained by the addition of espresso. In latte macchiato, espresso is added to milk and features more foam where the creaminess stands up to the roastiness of the extra shot of espresso, rather than simply hot milk. A latte macchiato often uses only half an espresso shot or less. Latte macchiato is often called as a \"layered\" coffee drink that consists of 3 parts from the top to bottom, espresso, macchia, and milk.
\n\nThe macchia is the little \"spot\" of crema left on top of the milk to clearly distinguish that the beverage is a latte macchiato where the espresso traditionally has been added before the milk, hence having no \"mark\".</string>
    <string name="espressoconpannatype_desc">Espresso con panna is a single or double shot of espresso topped with whipped cream which means \“espresso with cream\” in Italian. This coffee is the perfect introduction to espresso for those who are unsure they’re ready for the full-throttle intensity of a straight-up shot. The delicate dollop of whipped cream softens the rich and caramelly espresso flavors so exquisitely where people may choose to forego adding sugar altogether.</string>
    <string name="affogatotype_desc">Affogato is an Italian coffee-based dessert that usually takes the form of a scoop of vanilla gelato or ice cream topped or \"drowned\" with a shot of hot espresso. Some variations also include a shot of amaretto, bicerin, or other liqueur.
\n\nThough restaurants and cafes in Italy categorize the affogato as a dessert, some restaurants and cafes outside Italy categorize it as a beverage. Occasionally, coconut, berries, honeycomb and multiple flavors of ice cream are added.
</string>
    <string name="lattetype_desc">Latte or caffè latte is a coffee drink with espresso and steamed milk. Coffee and milk have been part of European cuisine since the 17<sup>th</sup> century. Caffè latte, Milchkaffee, café au lait and café con leche are domestic terms of traditional ways of drinking coffee, usually as part of breakfast in the home.\n\nPublic cafés in Europe and the US it seems have no mention of the terms until the 20<sup>th</sup> century, although Kapuziner is mentioned in Austrian coffee houses in Vienna and Trieste in the 2<sup>nd</sup> half of 1700s as \"coffee with cream, spices and sugar\" (being the origin of the Italian cappuccino). Originated from Italy, where caffè latte is almost always prepared at home, for breakfast only. The coffee is brewed with a stovetop Moka pot and poured into a cup containing heated milk. Outside Italy, latte is often sweetened.</string>
    <string name="cortadotype_desc">Cortado is a general term for a beverage consisting of espresso mixed with a roughly equal amount of warm milk to reduce the acidity from Spain. The milk in a cortado is steamed, but not frothy and "texturized" as in many Italian coffee drinks. The word cortado is the past participle of the Spanish verb cortar (to cut), in the sense of \"dilute\", and can refer variously to either coffee or espresso drinks throughout Spain, Portugal and Cuba.</string>


</resources>
